Hello, everyone, we meet again.
This time we not only have a talk session,
we also have a manager.
Thank you very much for your enthusiasm.
It can make our position full of joy and laughter.
I hope everyone can continue to pay attention to the software of Marvelous Design in the future.
We will also have more and more interaction with you on our community platform.
More and more game customers use the process of Marvelous to UE.
So when I was communicating with customers,
I gradually became familiar with this process.
The introduction of Marvelous to UE and data interconnection are very convenient.
After using MD,
we can start from GB,
the process of layout,
and then turn to this side.
It will save a lot of time collecting materials.
It greatly improves the efficiency of work.
I have been using Marvelous to UE for six years.
I think the professionalism of this software is incomparable.
Currently, the combination of MD and UE is very smooth.
I am particularly concerned about the AI generation version of Marvelous to UE.
It can help developers
to reduce the threshold of creation
and improve the efficiency of creation.
In addition,
I also look forward to the future of MD
to develop the function of creating clothes directly in UE.